(nervous chuckle)
(Howard:)Like off the map.
Like every American Idol winner
since season four.
(Bernadette:)Come on, Howard,
you're overreacting.
(Howard:)Am I?
(whispers):
Am I?
Wha... what do you want to bet
some black ops guy
(Howard:)is reprinting
my high school yearbook
(Howard:)and I'm no longer in it?
(Howard:)That chess club picture is now
(Howard:)just David Zimmerman
and Elaine Cho.
(Raj:)Okay, look,
I'm on the Air Force Web site,
(Raj:)and the department
that e-mailed you
(Raj:)is in charge of acquisitions.
(Raj:)So maybe they just
want to give you
(Raj:)a lot of money
for your invention.
(Howard:)Oh, please, that's
not how it works.
You saw E.T., Avatar,
Jurassic World.
(Howard:)The military just shows up
and takes over.
(Bernadette:)You do realize those weren't
documentaries, right?
(chuckles)
(Howard:)I'm sorry, you find this funny?
(Raj:)No, I was just thinking
about Jurassic World.
(Raj:)Boy, that was terrible.